hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft it's
been a while it's been a few weeks i
have been
actually quite ill with a cold but i'm
back now and happy new year everyone
welcome to 2020 we have some very
exciting things that's going to happen
on this channel this year hopefully i
don't know the future but what we are
here to do is to finally declare the
winner of demise and hand out all of
these dimendos and the winner was iskal
of course i don't know if everyone's
been keeping up but at the last minute
our
trap demised dock and crowned iskal the
winner who i believe still hasn't
actually died
yet but i actually thought to myself
let's do a quick ceremony for iskall he
is actually online right now so what
we'll do is we'll get hold of him and
we're going to present him with all
these diamonds but actually i think we
should scare him as well i mean he
hasn't actually died in demise but i
wanted to feel like he's gonna get
trapped so let's transform this whole
thing which is now finite it's now
finished into a stage
to present iskall with those diamonds
now this shouldn't do any actual damage
but it should scare him a little bit
so if i put a lectern here this will be
like his speech podium and i can even
make it look like there's going to be
some fireworks involved just so that he
he doesn't suspect anything especially
if there is a redstone button so it
turns out i don't know redstone very
well i've
i've had to extend this out a little bit
so he's actually going to stand all the
way out here
and i'm going to have to do a bit of a
redstone trickery to make this work
so it's going to be a couple of tnt
minecarts it's really simple i'm not
actually going to attempt to kill isko
at all because i i am still a secret bro
i am still secret bro i just want to
scare him a little bit i'm even gonna
put some like fake fireworks in here to
make it just in case he opens these
dispensers being all suspicious i bet
that paranoia hasn't quite left him yet
but he'll see some fireworks and
hopefully won't look too closely at them
so this is a really really simple trap
i've uh i've come to learn a little bit
too much about tnt minecarts i think
whoa
um
the heck
there's already been some sort of
accident here by the looks of things so
i'll put a not too subtle button
right here and i'll label this
fireworks
this is my like last chance to do a nice
trap i think uh because demise is ending
so this will be awesome so he'll see
this he'll see fireworks he will
probably you know he won't think too
much of it
all we got to do now is plant
this together
and then oops and then we seal it all
and act like everything is a okay i mean
that's a pretty obvious so maybe we
maybe we should do a um a little bit of
uh hiding there
but because because of the whole
fireworks ruse
it should in theory
give him no reason to suspect a thing
there we go job is done
and
yeah i think that's pretty much it i
don't think we'll hit any of the
diamonds with this explosion it should
be fairly small and because there's only
two tnt it will neither do enough damage
to kill him and enough damage to well i
mean there's already a crater under
there so i'm not really changing
anything so this is the end of demise
this is going to be
the final declaration of the winner but
before i hope no one sees this
before i get to do this because if
someone if there's anyone out there on
the hermitcraft server that's like me
and can't resist pressing a button
yeah that's going to go up in flames
well hopefully we'll get iscow on
quick enough to do it but before that i
actually i want to get rid of this black
and white skin now i'm totally
monochrome still and frankly i want to
have my red shirt back
so
this thing has popped up out of nowhere
by mumbo jumbo and it
looks
weird i got a message saying that you
should check this out so let's have a
quick look
welcome to the saturator if you're
reading this you're probably dead and
have a horrible gray skin and you
probably smell
you're not wrong he's not wrong i can't
fix the smell but i can fix your skin
with this saturator all you have to do
is jump inside the machine will activate
automatically and you will be
revitalized open once everyone's died
well isc hasn't died but i think he
means the end of demise let's let's just
go and do it
whoa
oh wow this is awesome
this is awesome
even the little song
is that it
are we done
is there nothing else
did it work
oh whoa
oh
oh dear
i'm uh i think um i think i might be a
little bit over saturated
oh my goodness i look like a bad
minecraft thumbnail i am
so oversaturated this is
this is ridiculous you can wait have i
got i've got weird colors on my trousers
i didn't know that those were red and
blue pixels on there this has revealed a
lot about my skin i do look quite
healthy though don't i look like i'm
glowing at all i look a little bit
radioactive well i'm sure that'll die
down in a few episodes time i hope but
one thing that i also wanted to do and
it kind of pains me but i'm not getting
any use out of it it's this building
here i absolutely love this building the
look of it the feel of it the grandeur
but it's just not getting any use i'm
not going to finish this project
i
still i still have the uh the bdubs uh
resource back on
it i'm just not getting any use out of
it i'm not gonna finish it so
i'm gonna do the mature thing and i'm
gonna sell it i don't know how much it's
worth but it is going to be up for sale
not including whoa not including some of
the valuables i got in here
oh my goodness look at all this iron
all right i need to
i need to be careful here and stock up
on everything useful
okay everything else all of this content
is uh with the sale so congratulations
to whoever whoever takes all this stuff
there we go
right everything valuable is out
it's a little bit of a shame but the
reality is i don't want to do this
project and it's time that i was honest
with myself and not just leave it here
to sit and collect dust so what we're
going to do
is put it for
sale
and uh how much should i charge
bargain price for a bit of prime retail
for
let's say 100 diamonds there we go for
sale 100 diamonds the whole thing it's
yours it's that's that's a good price
right that's a good price that's hours
of building loads of resources in there
and it's made i mean it's made out of
some expensive stuff as well um there's
loads of anvils up there i believe so
there you go for sale does anybody want
this mansion
anybody at all
anyone
oh
finally okay lol took him long enough
i've been i've been waiting for ages for
him to respond okay sweet uh i'll guess
i'll just wait for him here hello
what is wrong with your face i'm sorry
but you look like a like a tiger um i'm
back to the living room i'm a little i'm
a little bit too alive i think um
mumbo's machine has made me radioactive
wow
yeah it had an effect on me as well as
you can see i mean i'm still a brawl so
my head is fine
you're all multi-colored is it good in
that diamond armor yeah
it feels so good to be back in diamond
armor and not have to take too much
damage are you keeping the gold stuff on
i have set a challenge for myself i'm
gonna i'm gonna continue the demise i
know it's just me around still and i
know that no one's trying to trap me i'm
just you know
let's see how far it goes for the bros
so you're going to go solo bro low on
this one solo bro lord di maestro yeah
okay well as you know as winner of
demise uh i need to crown you officially
um all of these diamonds are yours they
are your diamonds i am so excited about
that i'm not gonna lie i'm so excited
about that so i'm i'm actually gonna
we're gonna do like a two-man
presentation here so i'm gonna take take
to the stands make this all official and
stuff um oh that this is this i've i've
made a proper presentation here okay
okay okay sorry sorry sorry i'm just
still in that device mode you know i
don't want to be you know all right
don't be trapped we're going to present
to um
no one
it's just you just you and me so right
are you ready for this i am very proud
to present to you iskall this skeleton
handful of diamonds as the official
winner of demise but before you do that
i'm going to need some evidence we all
know that you survived we all know you
didn't die but could you please for the
sake of proving it to everyone go into
your statistics and tell me the last
time since death or the play time since
death yes it is 4.77
days four point seventy seven days
that's i mean that's a lot of play time
that's not like that's not like just
four that's not just five days that's
days on the server that you've been on
yeah yeah
it's like it's like 140 hours that's 140
hours that is a lot of time
so
i'm very proud and very honored to
present to you these diamonds
yay
speak to you speech speech speech speech
speech i want to thank i wanna i wanna
thank my my bros yeah i wanna thank my i
wanna thank my my my my green bro and
that's uh i didn't prepare sp
um that that um
i'm just so grateful i'm just so excited
let's just let's just yeah let's just
celebrate with the fire all right
you gotta be kidding me dude
[Laughter]
this is the second time i'm in this hole
did someone else do this to you
i found that hole
i found that hole when i was making this
oh
dude what
i wasn't i wasn't really gonna demise
you i just i just was shaking dude i am
shaking how many hearts did i get you
because it was uh calculated
zero
hearts did no damage i don't think it
did damage dude what i don't think so no
well at least uh i got shocked anyway
those diamonds are for you to collect um
if i remember correctly though there was
a little it was a little side deal
there's a little deal on the side
there's a little bro
absolutely i'm gonna honor the bro pack
yes let me just get the honor of first
mining the diamond blocks
that's a lot of diamonds
i know that's it that's so shiny
diamonds
i
i did not expect to win this green i i
was thinking about traps to make well
you're lucky we had the bro pack because
otherwise i would have been after you
but yeah i know you wouldn't i did i
helped you secure the victory i got doc
i got the last i got the last guy
that was a pretty that was a pretty good
trap that was that was very bro very bro
did we agree on any did we agree on any
percentage split for the for the bros
i have an idea in my mind i thought we
just split it down the middle i thought
it was a if i win i'll give you half if
i if you win you give me half i thought
that was the deal but you know
i have i have another suggestion
is it that you what i'm going to keep
all the diamonds and give me one
is
i'm going to honor the deal
uh but
let's do this i'm going to give you 45
blocks of diamonds okay
how many is that i'm gonna keep 45
blocks myself
and we're going to give our architect
brother and dragon brother
um
nine blocks yeah okay fine
let's finish i feel kind of bad we went
into the enemy and him
i logged off he stole him off on dying
died and then you feel he died right
after king survivor's guilt
i you know you know he also have colored
both of us
yeah works for me i'm happy i've got
some diamonds i can pay scar back
because i lost a bet
classic
thank thank you ever so much for
declaring me the winner and the best and
most handsome hermit and dude don't do
that to me again
i
i'm still shaking i'm still shaking dude
i think because you're continuing demise
i really wouldn't be surprised if that's
not the the last time that that happens
to you because i even though i'm i'm not
gonna do that i mean it was just a joke
maybe other people will be um
the original hole was created as a trap
to kill and i didn't realize it the mice
was over i came here there was a stupid
tree right in front of your beautiful
board i was like this is weird
i didn't think of it as a trap and took
it down
because i landed i landed on the ledge
here it was crazy
well congratulations
and thank you
yeah well keep keep surviving i guess
and enjoy your gold armor i'm going to
go and enjoy my goal my diamond armor
and i'm going to enjoy these diamonds
yeah
have fun there's a mini game called run
feels good to have a replenishment of
diamonds you know what it's weird isn't
it as soon as i get back to like a stack
of diamond blocks something comes up i
end up spending loads i just i end up
just getting back exactly where i
started anyway there's a few things that
i want to do before the end of this
episode and the biggest one means going
back to
sahara but while we're on the way there
i have a big favor to ask so as some of
you uh maybe not all of you but as some
of you know i actually own and run a
server with my friend salted whoa
that was weird okay it's not loading
this isn't safe
as i was saying maybe we'll walk and do
this as i was saying i co-own a server
called wincraft with a friend of mine
called salted and he has made a rather
beautiful trailer for the most recent
update on the server it's a little bit
on the spooky side not gonna lie but i
would be really appreciative if you
could give it a quick watch i'm gonna
play it right now it's a couple of
minutes long see what you think all
right you ready three two one here we go
wincraft
[Music]
oh
man salted is so good at making these
trailers honestly he's such a good video
editor anyway that was the update for
windcraft check it out there will be a
link in the description and the ip if
you want to check it out but anyway
let's head back
to sahara where i want to do something
that i really shouldn't be doing i'm not
gonna lie it was definitely my fault but
i shouldn't be the one to fix it i'm not
qualified so what we're going to do is
genuinely fix the concrete machine
because i basically want to finish my
base by creating two more of these at
the back of the build however i don't
have enough white concrete to do it and
um
i should really fix this this giant
mistake that was made
so
what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna i'm gonna put my redstone
costume on something that's going to
help me do this and then that's exactly
what we're gonna do we're gonna fix this
machine
ha ha i'm ready i am ready to do
redstone this is exactly what's needed
just this is how i'm going to learn
redstone right as soon as i wear this
thing i know exactly what to do
it turns out there's not actually many
tutorials for this thing
but um fortunately i have a few
screenshots from back when this was made
and i'm gonna try my best
to make it now i know for a fact that
there's like a specific order because
what this is is a tnt jupiter and it
does some really weird redstone trickery
and i have no idea how it works
but
the thing is if i can make most of it
mumbo or iskall will be able to do the
bit of minecraft trickery that i don't
know so anyway let's get into a little
time lapse of making this with my
mustache on
all right let's get into it so what
we're doing is well i'm yeah i'm copying
what was here before it was entirely my
fault what went on here before i broke
this it was a complete accident all i
was doing was using the concrete maker
and i accidentally managed to deload the
chunks that were in here and for some
reason i came back it was just
completely exploded i honestly don't
really know what i did but i came back
and it was all gone so that's on me and
that's why we're repairing it it was um
maybe a little bit hopeful of me to
expect mumbo to remake this but uh
hopefully i will get some brownie points
back for this little contraption right
here
there we go it is back together i'm now
going to tell mumbo that he can do
whatever jiggery poker he needs doing so
i haven't added the minecart and i
haven't added the tnt or the dead coral
that makes this work i could put it on
there but i genuinely just don't know
whether i'm going to blow everything up
if i do that so i think it's best we get
the expert in and uh that means i should
probably i should take off this because
i'm no longer in redstone mode there we
go i had to channel my inner mumbo jumbo
to get this done but it is exactly as it
was apart from the tnt stuff there so
that is a job well done as soon as mumbo
is back in business then we can get
ourselves enough
white concrete which i've been
stockpiling over here
which i've been stockpiling over here
in order to finish
my base because
like i said i've been wanting to do this
for a really long time
anyway i'm afraid that is it for today's
episode i've got to say a huge huge
thank you for being very very patient
for me you might be able to hear it in
my voice i'm still not well and every
time i try and record it pushes me back
so i'm really trying to relax as much as
possible
but at the end of the day i still need
to try and get videos done i'm really
stuck between a rock and a hard place
it's it's it's incredibly difficult but
i can still get some stuff done it just
it's just taking me a really long time
at the moment so thank you for your
patience but more importantly thank you
very much for watching and uh if you are
stuck for content then um why don't you
go check out wincraft which there is a
link for in the description thank you
very much for watching and good bye